

- 9080167674
- snekasubramanian98@gmail.com
- http://3.110.193.67/
- 3/70 South Street, Oottathur, Trichy.

SKILLS

Photoshop
Illustrate
Adobe XD
Figma
HTML 5
CSS 3
Sass
Bootstrap 5
JavaScript
React JS
WordPress
* * * * * *

LANGUAGES

- English
- Tamil

SNEKAS

UIIUX DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I have been working in the design industry for 2 years, with my most recent experience being UI/UX Developer at great design and Developer. I possess valuable skills such as good communication and high creativity that I believe make I am best suited for the position of UI/UX Developer in your company.

PORTFOLIO

https://www.behance.net/ssneka

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR UI/UX DEVLOPER

April 2022 - Present

Ninos IT Solution pvt.ltd.

 I have held responsible for the Bootstrap, React JS framework, and media queries for use with responsive web Application design.

UI/UX DESIGNER

September 2021 - April 2022

Ninos IT Solution pvt.ltd.

 I was held responsible with the Bootstrap framework and media queries for use with responsive web design

EDUCATION

GCES Trichy-2016 - 2020

BE - ECE - 6.5 %

Dhana Lakshmi Srinivasan Hr.sec school - 2014-2016

H.S.C - 84%

Government High school Oottathur - 2004 -2014

S.S.L.C - 91 %